迈克:哈!是他们让你穿这身衣服上船的吗?
Mike: Ha!That's what they make you wear at Captain Sub?
卢克:不,我只是喜欢穿戴得像条白鱼.
Luke: No, I just like to dress like Popeye.
迈克:我说,你刚开始工作,要知道有些人是很难对付的.
Mike: Look, when you get a new job, you do have to deal with difficult people.
卢克:你说的是顾客吗?
Luke: You mean like the customers?
迈克:不,你的家人.
Mike: No, like your family.
麦琪:哦,噢,水手们!
Maggie: Ahoy, matey!
杰森:准许登船!
Jason: Permission a board!
麦琪:再照一张,我要寄给在伦敦的开萝尔…
Maggie: Let me take one more to send to Carol in London...
迈克:好主意,妈妈.
Mike: That's a great idea, Mom, then we can put a different address on it,
我们在信封上换个地址写上,让她觉得我们搬家了.
and make her think we moved.
本:非常感谢,
Ben: Thanks a lot, Captain Crunch.
穷光蛋船长.爸爸一大早就用招聘启事把我叫醒.
Dad woke me up this morning with the want ads.
你找个工作上为了什么啊?
What do you need a job for anyway?
麦琪:哦,我知道.他是为了存钱上大学.
Maggie: Oh, I bet I know.He's saving for college.
卢克:但首先,要买头哈利猪.
Luke: But first, a custom Harley.
杰森:你攒钱为了买一头猪?
Jason: You're saving up to buy a Hog?
克莉丝:他想买猪?你连一只猫都不给我买.
Chrissy: He gets a Hog?You won't even let me get a kitten.
本:嘿,卢克,包里是什么?
Ben: Hey, Luke.What's in the bag?
卢克:只是我领的水手帽.
Luke: It's just my official Captain Sub hat.
麦琪:哦,戴上.我想拍张穿整套制服的相片.
Maggie: Well put in on.I want to take a picture of the entire uniform.
本:不,真的.
Ben: No, really.
麦琪:来吧,他们说制服让你像个男人.
Maggie: Come on, they say the uniform makes the man.
本:还不如说,制服让人像个三明治.
Ben: In this case the uniform makes the sandwich.
卢克:哦,我得走了.我老板开车来接我.
Luke: Well, I'd better get going.My boss is driving me to work.
杰森:你老板接你上班?我也想找个这样的工作.
Jason: Your boss drives you to work?I'd like to get a job like that.
卢克:哦,他们在找一个财会人员,如果你有兴趣的话.
Luke: Well, they're looking for a counter person if you're available.
杰森:本,听见了吗?本!本!
Jason: Ben, you hear that?Ben!Ben!
杰森:嘿,给你提个小建议,
Jason: Hey, I got a tip for you Luke.
卢克.你可以利用这次坐车的机会,好好地了解你的老板.
You take advantage of this car-pooling opportunity to get to know your boss.
他也许可以教你点什么.
He probably could teach you a thing or two.
杰森:退后!退后!大家别动.我来应付他.
Jason: Stay back!Stay back!Hold it here everybody.I can handle this.
卢克:不,不,不,西沃医生.这是凯文,我的老板.
Luke: No, no, no, Dr.Seaver.This is Kevin, my boss.
凯文:嘿,卢克!准备好去"跳摇滚"了吗?
Kevin: Hey, Luke!Ready to rock'n roll?
迈克:你工作第一周感觉如何?
Mike: So how was your first week at work?
卢克:哦,你面前的是一位新上任的…经理助理.
Luke: Well, you're now looking at the new...assistant manager.
迈克:又换了一顶傻瓜帽,呃?
Mike: Another dumb hat, huh?
卢克:你应该去看厕所管理员戴的那顶帽子.
Luke: You should see the hat the restroom supervisor has to wear.
麦琪:嘿,卢克.很高兴遇到你.我们发现你总是很晚才回来.
Maggie: Hey, Luke.Glad we caught you.We've noticed you've been keeping late hours.
卢克:哦,我工作到9点半呢.
Luke: Well, I work 'til 9:30.
杰森:是的,不过你总是11点以后才回来.
Jason: Yeah, but you've been getting home after 11:00.
卢克:哦,哦,凯文喜欢下班后去放松放松.
Luke: Well, well, Kevin thinks it's a good idea to unwind after work.
杰森:噢,你听那个家伙的.
Jason: Ooooh, you listen to a guy who's only working at Captain Sub until
也许他只是在船上工作到晚上,然后下船去干他的犯罪勾当.
he can get his criminal career off the ground?
麦琪:哦,你可以让凯文先把你送回家.
Maggie: Well, you could ask Kevin to drop you off at home,
然后,他爱上哪里放松就上哪里.
and then he can go unwind wherever he wants.
卢克:我可以…不,我不想这样.
Luke: I could...but, I don't want to.
麦琪:哦,那么,卢克,我们也许应该谈谈,给你实行宵禁了.
Maggie: Well, then, Luke.We maybe should talk about you having a curfew.
迈克:这是错误的.
Mike: Big mistake.
杰森:卢克,请你出去一下,好吗?
Jason: Luke, will you excuse us for a minute?
卢克:替我说句好话,我请你吃三明治.
Luke: Stick up for me, and I'll slip you a hoagie.
杰森:我希望在卢克面前,你不要跟我们意见相反.
Jason: I wish you wouldn't contradict us in front of Luke.
迈克:爸爸,对不起.我不是有意的.只是,你们非得搞什么宵禁,这纯粹是自找麻烦.
Mike: Dad, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.It's just that you were really cruising for trouble with that whole curfew thing.
杰森:哦,是吗?
Jason: Oh, we are?
迈克:是的,爸爸,卢克跟别人不一样.我是说…直说吧,
Mike: Yeah, Dad, Luke is a different breed of horse.I mean...let's face it.
你们对待开萝尔就像耕地的马;克莉丝是匹小马;本…哦,
You're used to Carol, who pulls the plough, and Chrissy, who's still a pony,
他是马的屁股.
and Ben...well, he's pretty much a horse's patoot.
迈克:但是,卢克就像我;他是一匹野马.
Mike: But Luke is like me; he's a wild mustang.
麦琪:哦,谢谢你,野马.
Maggie: Well, thank you Gabbie.
迈克:听我说…我觉得,如果你们想用栅栏把卢克围起来,他会一脚踢开的.
Mike: Look...my point is, is that you try to put a fence around Luke, he's just going to kick it over.
麦琪:迈克,要是用栅栏圈住你…
Maggie: Mike, where are you going with all this horse....
杰森:麦琪…
Jason: Maggie...
麦琪:…类推一下.
Maggie: ...analogy.
迈克:别实行宵禁.等他困了,
Mike: Don't give him a curfew,
他会老老实实地回到马棚的.
and he'll mosey on back to the barn as soon as he's sleepy.
麦琪:需要我提醒你吗?我们成功地抚养了4个孩子,
Maggie: Need I remind you that we have successfully raised four children,
而且你也有过宵禁?
and you had a curfew?
迈克:不,你们有过而已.我能打开窗户,还有梯子.
Mike: No, you had a curfew.I had an open window and a trellis.
杰森:迈克,我们要管好这个家,
Jason: Mike, we've got to run this house by our rules.
必须有规矩.
Luke is a foster child here,
卢克是个收养的孩子,我看没有理由不对他实行宵禁.
and I see no reason why he shouldn't have a curfew.
迈克:好吧,行,
Mike: Okay, all right, fine.
好.你们可以把旗杆竖起来,可我认为他不会坐上去的.
You can run it up the flagpole, but I don't think he'll sit on it.
杰森:卢克!
Jason: Luke!
麦琪:好吧,卢克,我们要求你工作日在10点回家,周末在11点回家.
Maggie: Okay, Luke, we want you in the house 10:00 on weekdays and 11:00 on weekends
卢克:好的.
Luke: Okay.
杰森:哦,你知道吗,这都是老顽固父母定下的规矩.
Jason: Well, what do you know; the wacky old parents pulled it off.
迈克:是的,埃德外公总出坏主意.
Mike: Yeah, and Mr.Ed really talks.
本:克莉丝…猜一猜形状.
Ben: Now, Chrissy...name the shape.
克莉丝:方的!
Chrissy: Square!
本:不对.抓紧时间,比方的要圆.
Ben: No, take your time, think rounder.
克莉丝:方的!
Chrissy: Square!
本:想一想,就像…馅饼…或者月亮.
Ben: Think like, think like....a pie...or the moon.
克莉丝:月亮馅饼?
Chrissy: Moon pie?
克莉丝:对不起,我猜的不好,是吗?
Chrissy: Sorry.I'm not doing so good, am I?
本:不,还好了.你最后25个题目答对了2个.
Ben: No, that's okay.You got two out of the last, uh, 25.
麦琪:干什么呢?你们在玩游戏吗?
Maggie: What's up?You guys playing some kind of game?
克莉丝:本在考我是不是有月经症状.
Chrissy: Ben's testing to see if I have PMS.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本:呃,是超感功能.我在做一份加分报告.这是埃尔哈德老师的科学课要求的.
Ben: Uh, ESP, mom.I'm doing an extra-credit report for Mr.Airhead's science class.
麦琪:埃尔哈德老师,就是这一年里一直让你难受的那个老师吗?
Maggie: Mr.Airheart, the teacher who's been giving you such a hard time all year?
本:是的.如果我不把平均分提高到B,
Ben: Yeah.And if I don't get my average up to a B,
他就不让我到海登天文馆,参加班级的野外考察活动.
he's not going to let me go on the class field trip to the Hayden Planetarium.
麦琪:哦,这样啊.
Maggie: Oh, well, Ben,
本,我和你爸爸很乐意带你去天文馆.
your father and I'd be happy to take you to the planetarium.
本:是的,不过,
Ben: Yes, but can you arrange for Sasha Sorotski to be sitting next to
你能安排萨莎索罗特斯基在黑暗之中坐在我旁边…穿着软毛衣?
me in the dark... wearing a fuzzy sweater.
麦琪:做梦.
Maggie: Gotcha!
迈克:本说你们想跟我谈谈?
Mike: Ben said you guys wanted to talk to me?
麦琪:是关于卢克的.
Maggie: It's about Luke.
杰森:我们打算承认,我们,呃…
Jason: We're ready to admit we, uh.....
迈克:…错了?
Mike: ...were wrong?
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
迈克:大错特错了?
Mike: Were very, very wrong?
麦琪:不,我们打算承认我们需要你的帮助.
Maggie: No, we're ready to admit that we need your help.
迈克:哦,我觉得你们的决定很正确.
Mike: Well, I think you made the right decision.
你们想抓住野马还是利用野马.
You want to catch a mustang, you gotta use a mustang.
让我直说吧…要我跟他说什么?
So let me get this straight...what is it that you want me to tell him?
杰森:实行宵禁!
Jason: He's grounded!
迈克:不能这样!
Mike: No stinking way!
杰森:如果一个孩子不能学着遵守家里的规矩,
Jason: If a kid can't learn to live by a family's rules,
他就永远不会学着遵守社会准则.迈克,
he'll never learn to live by society's, Mike.
你有责任教卢克遵守纪律.
Now you owe it to Luke to teach him some discipline.
迈克:我讨厌你们讲什么大道理.好,好,我跟他谈.
Mike: I hate it when you guys make sense.Okay, okay, I'll talk to him.
可如果他晚回来有充分的理由,
But if he's got a darn good reason for being late,
我不会无缘无故地教训他.
I'm not giving him any punishment.
迈克:卢克回来了.
Mike: Luke's home.
卢克:哦,哈罗.
Luke: Uh, hello.
迈克:嘿,卢克,现在11点15了,你知道意味着什么吗?
Mike: Hey, Luke.It's 11:15.You know what that means?
卢克:我错过了电视剧!
Luke: I'm missing Arsenio!
杰森:嘿·你该在10点就回家的.
Jason: Hey!You were supposed to be home by 10:00.
迈克:可我肯定他晚回来是有特殊原因的.
Mike: But I'm sure that he's got a darn good reason for being late.
快给他讲讲.
So, go ahead and give it to him.
卢克:哦,我去了游戏厅.那里有一台机器,能玩10个免费游戏.
Luke: Uh, I was at the arcade.We found a video machine with ten free games.
迈克:哦,那好吧,好吧,我没的选择了.你要…
Mike: Well, okay, okay.You give me no choice.You're....
麦琪:…被宵禁.
Maggie: ...grounded.
迈克:她说了.
Mike: What she said.
卢克:什么?不过,能从下周一开始吗?周五晚上有个重要的晚会.
Luke: What?But, well can it start Monday?There's a major party Friday night.
迈克:好的,没问题.
Mike: Okay, sure.
麦琪:迈克!你不能让在惩罚上他讨价还价.
Maggie: Mike!You can't let him trade punishments.
这不是"让我们做笔买卖".
This isn't "Let's Make a Deal."
迈克:可他穿的很像做买卖的.
Mike: Although he's dressed for it.
麦琪:宵禁包括不能参加晚会.
Maggie: The grounding includes missing the party.
卢克:我不明白你们为什么把我当孩子看.
Luke: I don't know why you're treating me like a kid.
我要11点上床,可我有3年根本就没有床.
I gotta be in bed by 11:00.I went three years with no bed.
我晚上就在中央公园睡.
I've spent the night in Central Park.
我碰到过匪徒,杀人犯,还看过不良青年的摇滚歌会.
I've survived gangs, murderers, and Pia Zadora's outdoor concert.
杰森:对不起,卢克,但这是为你好.
Jason: Sorry, Luke, but this is for your own good.
卢克:哦,不!这太严格了!
Luke: Oh, man!This sucks nickels!
迈克:晚安!
Mike: Good night.
卢克:哦,多谢了,迈克.
Luke: Well, thanks a lot, Mike.
迈克:嘿,嘿,
Mike: Hey, hey, hey.Don't look at me.You're the one who messed up, pal.
嘿.别看我.是你把一切都搞砸了,
Don't ever break curfew again...
老兄.别再违反宵禁规定了…至少要找个像样的理由啊.
without at least coming up with an airtight alibi.
本:…真倒霉.
Ben: ...My bummed
卢克:给我说说.
Luke: Tell me about that.
本:你有什么倒霉的?
Ben: What you bummed about?
卢克:外边有个晚会,我却在家里.
Luke: There's a party out there, and I'm in here!
本:你抱怨是因为你被"停飞"一周?我从1989年就被"停飞"了.
Ben: You're squawking about being grounded for a week?I was grounded for 1989.
卢克:那你的倒霉事是什么?
Luke: So what are you bummed about?
本:埃尔哈德那老头不收我的报告.他说超感功能是垃圾,不是科学.
Ben: Old Man Airhead threw my report out.He says ESP's a crock, not a science.
就因为他,另外会有人有机会从萨莎索罗特斯基的毛衣上摘毛球了.
Thanks to him, someone else is gonna be picking sweater pills off of Sasha Sorotski
卢克:那埃尔哈德是个老顽固.得有人好好地启发启发他.
Luke: That Airhead's a jerk.Somebody ought to fix him good.
本:我有了,我要向他证明世上真有超感功能,
Ben: I know; I'm gonna prove that ESP is real and that Chrissy has it.
Next to her, the Amazing Creskin's gonna look only mildly interesting
杰森:快点,麦琪,要不我们就错过开幕式了.
Jason: Come on, Maggie, or we'll miss the opening curtain.
麦琪:杰森,我从没见过你对一部晚场戏这么在意.
Maggie: Jason, I have never seen you this excited about dinner theater.
杰森:哦,
Jason: Well, how many times do you get to see Marla Maples and Jessica
你有几次机会看玛勒麦普勒斯和杰西卡哈恩演出呢?
Hahn in "The Odd Couple?"
麦琪:一次也没有.好吧,我们马上就去海罗佛特晚场剧院.
Maggie: None, if you're lucky.Okay, we'll be at the Hayloft Dinner Theater.
杰森:再见,卢克.
Jason: See you, Luke.
麦琪:晚安,卢克.
Maggie: Good night, Luke.
卢克:迈克,你回来了.你得给你父母谈一谈.
Luke: Mike, you're back.You've gotta talk to your parents.
迈克:谈什么?
Mike: Why?
卢克:你要给我求个情让我去参加那个晚会.
Luke: You've gotta talk them into letting me go to that party.
迈克:卢克,他们下决心了.我能怎么办?
Mike: Luke, they made up their mind.What can I do?
卢克:等一下.
Luke: Wait a minute.
你还是那个迈克西沃吗?
Aren't you the same Mike Seaver who convinced his parents that report
他曾经让父母相信学校因为保护树木而停止下发成绩单了.
cards were discontinued as a tree-saving measure?
迈克:我想如果你有这样的天赋,不用就是犯罪.
Mike: I guess when you've got the talent, it is a crime not to use it.
卢克:他们就在厨房里.
Luke: They're in the kitchen.
迈克:好吧,好吧,"西沃巧舌"开始行动.
Mike: Okay.All right.Silver-tongue is on the case.
迈克:妈妈!爸爸!我正在找你们呢?
Mike: Mom!Dad!Just the people I was looking for!
杰森:噢!每次他用这种口气讲话,
Jason: Oooh!Every time he uses that tone of voice,
我脖子后面的汗毛就立起来了.
the little hairs on the back of my neck stiffen.
麦琪:你又要花言巧语地哄骗我们吗,迈克?
Maggie: What are you trying to charm us out of now, Mike?
迈克:哦,不,不,不,不是我的事儿.呃,是关于卢克.我觉得他真的已经吸取教训了.
Mike: Oh, no, no, no.This isn't for me.Uh, this is about Luke.I think that he's really l earned his lesson,
我认为他的宵禁应该结束了,呃,
You see, I think that he's really l earned his lesson,
就从现在.
and I think his grounding should end, oh, about now.
杰森:哼哼!
Jason: Hmm-hmm!
麦琪:迈克,我们必须坚持原则.
Maggie: Mike, we have to take a stand.
杰森:如果我们现在就退让,我们就等于允许他凌驾与我们之上了.
Jason: If we back down now, we're giving him permission to walk all over us.
迈克:哦,我对此可不在乎.
Mike: Well, I can live with that.
麦琪:迈克,我们不能这样.既然你想来调停,你应该为卢克付有责任.
Maggie: Well, we can't.Mike, when you got into the middle of this, you took
on part of the responsibility for Luke
杰森:嘿,是你说他是一匹野马.
Jason: Hey, you're the one who speaks mustang.
你回去告诉他,他还被关在马场里.希望你进展顺利.
Just tell him he's still confined to the paddock.Happy trails.
麦琪:坚持立场.
Maggie: Stick to your guns.
迈克:我都自身难保了.
Mike: I hope I shoot myself in the foot.
卢克:迈克,你不知道我多么感激你给我争取来参加晚会的机会.
Luke: Mike, I can't tell you how much I appreciate you springing me for
你太好了,太伟大了,你是我的国王.
this party.You're the best, the greatest, the king.
迈克:你不能去.
Mike: You can't go.
卢克:你太软弱了.你是没问呢,还是站到他们那一边了?
Luke: You're slime.Did you even ask, or are you on their side now?
迈克:哦,行了,卢克.你别这个样子.卢克!卢克-!
Mike: Oh, come on, Luke.Don't be this way.Luke!Luke-ee!Luke-ster!Luke-inator!
卢克先生!卢克王子!好了,好了,我认输了,你可以走了.
All right, all right, all right, you're tearing me apart.You can go.
卢克:真的?
Luke: Really?
迈克:是的,好了.
Mike: Yes, fine.But you have to be home by your curfew.That's 11:00.
不过你必须在宵禁之前回来.就是11点.不能晚一分.
Not a minute later.
卢克:谢谢,谢谢.我就知道你对我最好.好棒.
Luke: Thank you, thank you.I didn't know if you'd come through or not.Yeah!
卢克:哦,你为我冒险了.
Luke: Well, you took a shot.
迈克:记住,卢克,11点.
Mike: Remember, Luke, 11:00.
麦琪:我忘了戏票了.
Maggie: I forgot the tickets.
你爸爸说是我的潜意识不想去看戏.
Your father thinks my subconscious doesn't want to go to the theater.
他错了;我的潜意识是想炸掉那家戏院.
He's wrong; my subconscious wants to blow up the theater.
迈克:太有意思了,妈妈,你最好快点!
Mike: That's funny, mom.You'd better hurry!
麦琪:迈克,你想赶我走吗?
Maggie: Mike, you trying to get rid of me?
迈克:不,不,不.真可笑.你快点吧!
Mike: No, no, no, that's ridiculous.Shake a leg!
麦琪:那是什么?
Maggie: What's that?
迈克:什么什么?
Mike: What's what?
卢克:走了!
Luke: Let's roll!
麦琪:你怎么让他走了?
Maggie: How could you let him go?
迈克:我受不了他发脾气的样子.
Mike: I couldn't stand to see him mad at me.
杰森:哦,得了吧.
Jason: Oh, come on.Kids don't like discipline.
孩子都不喜欢约束.记得吗,
Remember when you planted Ben to see if he'd grow?
你曾经把本埋到土里看他是不是长出来.我们惩罚了你;你好一阵发火.
We punished you; you got angry with us.
迈克:不,我没有.
Mike: No, I didn't.
麦琪:哦,是的,你发火了.你还在爸爸的短裤上写上"同性恋"的字样.
Maggie: Oh, yes you did.You lined your father's shorts with Ben-Gay.
迈克:哦,对,我忘了.
Mike: Oh, right.I forgot.
杰森:我可忘不了.
Jason: I never will.
麦琪:我也忘不了.
Maggie: Neither will I.
迈克:你们俩到底担心什么呢?他答应我在11点之前就回家的.
Mike: What are you guys so worried about?He promised me he'd be home by 11:00.
麦琪:哦,要不是你乱搀和,他根本不应该出去.
Maggie: Well, he wasn't supposed to go out at all until you got involved.
迈克:妈妈,你不愿意他坏规矩,
Mike: Mom, you were tired of him breaking the rules,
所以我 给他定了一条他可以忍受的规矩.
so I just gave him one that he could live with.
麦琪:你想什么呢,迈克,
Maggie: What do you think, Mike, that these rules are arbitrary?
这些规矩是随意定的吗?我们拿规矩闹着玩吗?
That we just pull them out of a hat?
迈克:哦,我实在不知道你们是为什么.
Mike: Well, I've never actually seen the hat.
麦琪:噢!
Maggie: Ooh!
杰森:我们是在浪费时间.有一天你会明白的,迈克,当你有了孩子的时候.
Jason: We're wasting our time.You will understand one day, Mike, when you have kids of your own.
克莉丝:我都记住了.
Chrissy: I got it memorized.
第一张卡片是方块,然后分别是圆形,星星,椭圆,
First card's square, then circle, then star, rectangle, triangle, wavy lines,
三角,曲折线;你摸耳朵是红色,你揪鼻子是绿色.
red if you touch your ear, green if you pick your nose.
本:是摸我的鼻子!你必须要记住,亲爱的,这很重要.
Ben: Touch my nose!You've got to remember, honey, this is really important.
克莉丝:我知道…萨莎的毛衣棒极了.
Chrissy: I know...Sasha sweater super-nervous.
本:克莉丝,如果我成功了,
Ben: Chrissy, if we pull this off,
我这个月每天都陪你玩"茶话会"游戏.
I'll play tea-party with you every day this month.
本:埃尔哈德先生,很荣幸.
Ben: Mr.Airheart, what a pleasure.
埃尔哈德:西沃,如果这次的演示结果没有能达到我们预期的效果,
Airheart: Seaver, if this little demonstration of yours doesn't produce
你不仅被剥夺野外参观的机会,
some quantifiable results, not only will you be barred from the field trip,
而且我的课你也很难及格了.
you'll be lucky to get a passing grade in my class.
本:埃尔哈德老师,我们的关系总是这么紧张.
Ben: Mr.Airheart, we've had a rocky relationship.
埃尔哈德:哈!
Airheart: Hah!
本:我们为什么不缓和一下呢?
Ben: Why don't we bury the hatchet?
克莉丝:很高兴见到您,埃尔哈德先生.
Chrissy: Pleased to meet you Mr.Airhead.
埃尔哈德:呃?
Airheart: Hmm?
本:如果你坐在那里,我们就开始了.
Ben: If you'll just sit over here, we'll begin.
本:克莉丝?好了吗?
Ben: Chrissy?You ready?
克莉丝:方块.
Chrissy: Square.
本:不,亲爱的,还没开始呢.
Ben: No, honey, we haven't started yet.
克莉丝:圆形.
Chrissy: Circle.
本:嘿,你怎么都知道!前两个都对了.太神奇了,太奇妙了.
Ben: Hey, what do you know!The first two are correct!Goosepimples, goosepimples.
埃尔哈德:对不起,超人,
Airheart: Excuse me, Carnac, but before you proceed,
在你们开始之前,介意我看看那些卡片吗?
do you mind if I see those cards?
埃尔哈德:我答应还给你们的.(翻卡片)现在可以开始了.
Airheart: I promise I'll return them.(shuffling cards) Now you may begin.
本:好的.克莉丝,我希望你把脑子变的空灵起来.
Ben: Okay, Chrissy, I want you to make your mind a total blank.
埃尔哈德:她跟你是一体的;这并不太难.
Airheart: She's related to you; that shouldn't be difficult.
本:克莉丝,请你猜猜卡片上的东西.
Ben: Now, Chrissy, I want you to guess what's on these cards.
你不知道我多么希望你能猜出卡片上的东西.
You have no idea how much I want you to guess what's on these cards.
克莉丝:椭圆形.
Chrissy: A rectangle.
本:对了.
Ben: That's right!
埃尔哈德:噢?
Airheart: Huhn!
本:好的.
Ben: Okay.
克莉丝:三角.
Chrissy: A triangle.
本:怎么会!我是说,好孩子.
Ben: How the heck!I mean, good girl.
埃尔哈德:你能看透卡片吗?
Airheart: Can you see through this?
克莉丝:不能!快点啊.
Chrissy: Nope!Let's go faster.
克莉丝:钻石形…星星…正方形…圆形…红圆…
Chrissy: Diamond...star...square...circle...red circle...
埃尔哈德:这,这,这太奇怪了!
Airheart: This, this, this is astonishing!
本:我也这么想!我是说,如果她能让勺子弯曲,我早来了.
Ben: You're telling me!I mean, if she starts bending spoons, I'm outta here.
埃尔哈德:听着,我不知道你俩怎么搞的,
Airheart: Look, I don't know what you two are up to,
但这里面有什么把戏.
but this has got to be some kind of a trick.
本:先生,你自己把卡片都翻过了.
Ben: Sir, you shuffled the cards yourself.
埃尔哈德:我,呃,我不明白.
Airheart: I, uh, I don't understand this.
本:先生,我花了很大力气才搞成这个实验.
Ben: Sir, I worked very hard on setting up this experiment.
咱俩都知道,我不是一个差劲的学生,
We both know I'm not a bad student, and I deserve a B.
我应该得个B,我也应该去参观天文馆.
I also deserve to go on that field trip.
埃尔哈德:啊,我答应.
Airheart: Oh, why not.
为什么不呢?我从没见过一个学生为了去天文馆会这么用功.
Why, I've never seen a student work so hard to get to the planetarium.
本:天文学是我的生命!
Ben: Astronomy is my life!
埃尔哈德:萨莎·索罗特斯基也不错吧.
Airheart: Sasha Sorotski isn't so bad either.
本:克莉丝,你真的猜出我拿的是什么吗?
Ben: Chrissy, you actually guessed what I was holding up?
克莉丝:怎么会呢?我看起来像什么,一个算卦的?
Chrissy: Are you kidding?What do I look like, a mind-reader?
本:哦,那么,这次和上次有什么不一样呢?
Ben: Well, then, what's the difference between this time and last time?
克莉丝:上次,我看不到你眼镜片发射过来的东西.
Chrissy: Last time I couldn't see the reflection in your glasses.
本:那么,那些"茶话会",我坐在特迪熊边上呢,还是你边上?
Ben: So, these tea parties; do I sit next to Mr.Teddybear, or by you?
克莉丝:我边上.
Chrissy: By me.
迈克:好了,好了,10点59分,他到家肯定11点整.卢克是个负责的孩子.我能按他的进门的时间对我的表.
Mike: Ok, ok.10:59, He'll be home by 11:00.Luke's a responsible kid.I can set my watch by the Luke-meister.
电视播音员:现在是11点.你知道你们的孩子在哪里吗?
TV Announcer: It's 11:00, do you know where your children are?
电视播音员:由于有一辆装小鸡的车翻了,
TV Announcer: Two lanes of the Long Island Expressway have been temporarily
长岛高速路两侧的单行道暂时关闭.
closed, due to an overturned chicken truck.Guess you'd better steer clear.
您最好改道行驶并注意交通安全.
Offering biscuits and gravy.
迈克:小鸡!我讨厌碰到这种事.
Mike: Chickens!I'd hate to be caught in that mess.
迈克:严重吗?
Mike: How bad is it?
护士:代号F!代号F!
Nurse: Code F!Code F!
迈克:哦,这是什么意思啊?
Mike: Well, what does that mean?
医生:我必须做羽毛切除手术.还有希望,他是个勇敢的小小伙子.护士!
Doctor: I'll have to do a feather-ectomy.There's hope, he's a plucky little guy.Nurse!
护士:是,医生.
Nurse: Yes, doctor.
医生:钳子.
Doctor: Tweezers
护士:钳子.
Nurse: Tweezers.
迈克:卢克,卢克!能听见我吗?你怎么样?
Mike: Luke, Luke!Can you hear me?Are you all right?
卢克:(虚弱地)是你吗,迈克?
Luke: (spitting) Is that you, Mike?
迈克:是我,是我.我就在这里.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, it's me.I'm right here.
卢克:你为什么不阻止我去参加晚会呢?
Luke: Why didn't you stop me from going to the party?
医生:对不起,西沃先生,但只有一件事我们可以做了.
Doctor: I'm sorry, Mr.Seaver, but there's only one more thing I can do.
迈克:是什么?
Mike: What is it?
医生:我要叫一个专家.护士!
Doctor: I'll have to call in a specialist.Nurse!
护士:是,医生.
Nurse: Yes, doctor.
医生:给桑德罗上校打电话.
Doctor: Get Colonel Sanders on the phone.
护士:桑德罗上校死了,先生.
Nurse: Colonel Sanders is dead, sir.
医生:噢-哦!
Doctor: Oh-oh!
迈克:哦,天啊,
Mike: Oh come on, what kind of trouble could he possibly get into?
他也许会卷到什么麻烦事儿里去呢?我是说他不会胡来的.
I mean, it's not like he's wild.
台球玩家:天不早了,布鲁沃尔,你是不该回家了?
Pool Player: It's kinda late, Brower, shouldn't you be getting home?
卢克:(笑)我的监护人是个十足的笨蛋,他被我训练地像只长耳朵狗.
Luke: (laughing) My guardian's the perfect sap!I've got him trained like a cocker spaniel
台球玩家:(笑)有只宠物真不错.
Pool Player: (laughing) It's nice to have a pet.
卢克:嘿,服务生!给每个人来一杯鲜啤酒!把瓶子放这.
Luke: Hey, bartender!Another round of root-beer floats!And leave the bottle!
迈克:我懂了!咳,妈妈是对的!11点以后还不知发生什么事儿呢.他会撒野;
Mike: I knew it!Gosh, mom was right!There's no telling what could happen after 11:00.He could run wild.
他会犯法;他会走上犯罪的道路.
He could break the law.He could take up a life of crime.
牧师:我的孩子,你还有什么要最后忏悔?
Priest: My son, do you have any last confessions?
卢克:我喜欢过交际花.
Luke: I liked Ishtar.
牧师:那会毁了你的.有什么人想让我联系吗?
Priest: That'll cost you.Is there anyone you'd like me to contact?
卢克:叫迈克西沃.就因为他,
Luke: Call Mike Seaver.
我才变野了,破坏宵禁,
Thanks to him, I ran wild, broke curfew, and took up a life of crime.
后来又开始犯罪.怎么突然出现回声了?
How come suddenly there's an echo?
牧师:我们只是用在关键词上.好了,
Priest: We only use it on the important words.Well, the chair is waiting.
他们都在等着呢.我们去吧.对不起.
Let's get cookin'.Sorry.
迈克:他喜欢过交际花?
Mike: He liked Ishtar?
迈克:卢克,卢克!你知道现在几点了吗?
Mike: Luke, Luke!Do you have any idea what time it is?
卢克:嘿,我是破坏了宵禁,
Luke: Hey, I guess I blew it with that curfew thing,
但至少我打败了你的父母.
but at least I beat your parent home.
迈克:嘿,先别说我的父母,你先回答我.
Mike: Hey, forget about my parents.You've got to answer to me.
卢克:迈克!迈克--!迈克王子!
Luke: Mike!Mike-ee!Mike-a-maniac!
迈克:嘿,别叫我迈克王子!你被"停飞"了.
Mike: Hey, don't you Mike-a-maniac me!You're grounded.
卢克:什么?
Luke: What?
迈克:一个月.
Mike: For one month.
卢克:开玩笑!
Luke: You're kidding!
迈克:不,
Mike: No, I'm not kidding.
我没有.你知道你今晚让我多担心吗?
Do you have any idea what you put me through tonight?
我是说我幻想着你死了!
I mean, I'm imagining that you're dead.
担心能不能再见你.
Wondering if I'm ever gonna see you again.
卢克:嘿,我做的事情,你都做了无数遍了.
Luke: Hey, I didn't do anything you haven't done a million times.
迈克:哦,可那不一样,卢克.
Mike: Well, that was different, Luke.
我那样做不是为自己,是给父母看的.
I didn't do it to me; I did it to my parents.
现在我知道他们的感受;他们只是想保护我.哦,哇噢,
Now I know how they felt; they were just protecting me.Oh, whoa!
听我说!如果下次我再纵容你,
Listen to me!Next thing you know,
我就买双白鞋绑在自己的胸脯上.
I'll be wearing white shoes and my belt up around my nipples.
杰森:就这样,卢克,你被"停飞"了,这次我是下定决心了.
Jason: That's it, Luke.You're grounded, and this time we mean business.
麦琪:两周.
Maggie: Two weeks.
迈克:嘿,嘿,我已经"停飞"他一个月了.
Mike: Hey, hey, I grounded him for a month.
杰森:一个月?有点重了吧?
Jason: A month?Isn't that a little severe?
迈克:爸爸,别这样.不要在孩--子的面前破坏我的威信.
Mike: Dad, please.Do not undermine me in front of the K-I-D.
现在听着,先生,我要你回到自己的房间,
Now listen, mister, I want you to march up to your room,
好好想想你都干了些什么.我是认真的,还有收起你脸上的那种表情.
and think about what you've done.I'm serious.And wipe that look off your face.
卢克:哎吆!
Luke: Phew!
麦琪:迈克,你想重新考虑一下吗?你对他太严厉了.
Maggie: Mike, don't you want to reconsider?You were a little rough on him.
迈克:等你有了孩子,你就会明白了.
Mike: You'll understand when you have kids.
麦琪:嘘!别告诉迈克,我给你多拿了一些甜点.
Maggie: Shh!Don't tell Mike, but I brought you up a little extra dessert.
卢克:谢谢!
Luke: Thanks!
麦琪:我正在劝他,让他给你改过自新的机会.
Maggie: I'm still working on him to give you time off for good behavior.
卢克:谢谢!
Luke: Thanks!
杰森:嗨,卢克,迈克呢?
Jason: Hi, Luke.Where's Mike?
卢克:哦,我没见着他.
Luke: Uh, I haven't seen him.
杰森:好.这样,哦,我知道他不准你看电视,不过…
Jason: Good.So, uh, I know he said no more TV, but...
卢克:电视!
Luke: TV!
杰森:嘘!藏起来,藏起来.我没来过.
Jason: Shh!Just put it away.Put it away.I was never here.
卢克:好啊,你在监视我.
Luke: Great, you're spying on me.
迈克:卢克,"停飞"了这么久,你该吸取教训了吧.
Mike: Luke, it's time you learned something from being grounded.
卢克:天啊,你太狠了.什么,你要给窗户上栏杆吗?
Luke: Boy, you don't let up.What, are you measuring the window for bars?
迈克:不!是你学习如何逃跑的时候了.快点.
Mike: No!It's time you learned how to sneak out.Come on!
卢克:但这是你的惩罚.
Luke: But this is your punishment.
迈克:我知道.如果你说出去,你就被"停飞".冲啊!
卢克:迈克!
00:22:14,200
Mike: I know.And if you say anything, you're grounded.Let's go! Luke: Mike!